A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, Program Files (Non-Grant), RG 5 FA1799
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Endowment Files, 1983-2015; 2; 27.53 Cubic Feet 72 letter document boxes and 1 half-letter box
  - Gulf Coast Community Foundation, 20030144, 2003 September 9-2005 September 9 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Grant 20030144, Gulf Coast Community Foundation, $1 million. For donor-advised funds.
  - Henry Ford Health System, 20040253, 2004 November 1-2005 November 1 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 3691
    Grant 20040253, Henry Ford Health System, $5,000. Trustee-recommended grant (Noland): For the Gail and Lois Warden Endowed Chair in Multicultural Health. 9/1/11: CHANGED CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING SUPPORT. TRUSTEE GRANTS WILL NOT BE INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT PORTFOLIO GOING FORWARD.
  - New Detroit, 9800234, 1998 December 8-2005 December 8 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3141
    Grant 9800234, New Detroit, $100,000 for a visioning process to develop a strategic plan addressing youth violence in Detroit's Empowerment Zone, as part of the youth violence prevention/Youth Development Initiative.
  - The Saint Paul Foundation, 20030147, 2003 September 9-2005 September 9 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
    Knight File Number - 3692
    Grant 20030147, The Saint Paul Foundation, $1.8 Million. For donor-advised fund. (2 folders)
  - South Dakota Community Foundation, 20040173, 2004 September 14-2005 September 14 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 3693
    Grant 20040173, South Dakota Community Foundation, $1.5 million to establish a donor-advised fund.
  - University of Georgia Foundation, 20040101, 2004 June 15-2005 June 15 (Box 53, Folder 4, Box 54, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 3694
    Grant 20040101, University of Georgia Foundation, $1.5 million to endow a Knight chair in health and medical journalism. (2 folders, folder 2 is in box 54)
  - Akron Community Foundation, 20020455, 2002 December 10-2006 December 10 (Box 54, Folder 2-3)
    Knight File Number - 4017
    Akron Community Foundation, 20020455, $3.4 million. For community foundation donor-advised funds. (2 folders)
  - Centre County Community Foundation, 20030172, 2003 December 9-2006 December 9 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4018
    Centre County Community Foundation, 20030172 grant, $400,000. For a challenge grant to build up an administrative endowment. 8/12/11: WAS CODED AS ENDOWMENT. REMOVED CODING AS TYPE OF SUPPORT AND NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT MANAGEMENT GOING FORWARD.
  - Community Foundation for Southeastern Michigan, 20020463, 2002 December 10-2006 December 10 (Box 55, Folder 2-3)
    Knight File Number - 4019
    Grant 20020463, Community Foundation for Southeastern Michigan, $3,750,000. For community foundation donor advised funds. (2 folders)
  - Community Foundation of the Chattahoochee Valley, 20020458, 2002 December 10-2006 December 10 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4020
    Grant 20020458, Community Foundation of the Chattahoochee Valley, $2,500,000. To establish a donor-advised fund.
  - Dade Community Foundation, Inc. (now The Miami Foundation, Inc.) 20030131, 2003 September 9-2006 September 9 (Box 56, Folder 2, Box 57, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4022
    Grant 20030131, Dade Community Foundation, Inc. (now The Miami Foundation, Inc.) $3,720,000. For donor advised funds. (2 folders. Folder 2 in in box 57)
  - Foundation for the Carolinas, 20020460, 2002 December 10-2006 December 10 (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
    Knight File Number - 4023
    Grant 20020460, Foundation for the Carolinas, $3,750,000. For community foundation donor advised funds.
  - Henry Ford Health System, 20050274, 2005 November 1-2006 November 1 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 4068
    Grant 20050274, Henry Ford Health System, $5,000. Trustee-recommended (Noland): For the Gail and Lois Warden Endowed Chair in Multicultural Health. 9/1/11: CHANGED CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING SUPPORT. TRUSTEE GRANTS WILL NOT BE INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT PORTFOLIO GOING FORWARD.
  - Johnson and Wales University, 20050221, 2005 November 1-2006 November 1 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4069
    Grant 20050221, Johnson & Wales University, $50,000 for an endowment fund for scholarships for returning Charlotte students. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Legacy Foundation Inc., 20020461, 2002 December 10-2006 December 10 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 4024
    Grant 20020461, Legacy Foundation Inc.$2,500,000. To establish a Knight donor-advised fund.
  - The Philadelphia Foundation, 20030146, 2003 September 9-2006 September 9 (Box 58, Folder 3, Box 59, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4025
    Grant 20030146, The Philadelphia Foundation, $3,450,000. For donor advised funds. (2 folders. Folder 2 is in box 59)
  - Community Foundation Silicon Valley, 20030143, 2003 September 9-2006 September 9 (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
    Knight File Number - 4021
    Grant Silicon Valley Community Foundation, 20030143, $3,750,000. For donor-advised funds. (2 folders)
  - Student Press Law Center, 20030020, 2003 March 11-2006 March 11 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4070
    Grant 20030020, Student Press Law Center, $1.5 million (partial challenge over three years). For operating support and to launch an endowment campaign.
  - Western Reserve Academy, 20050014, 2005 March 1-2006 March 1 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 4071
    Grant 20050014, Western Reserve Academy, $20,000. Trustee-Recommended grant (Austen): For the endowment for faculty advancement. 9/1/11: CHANGED CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING SUPPORT. TRUSTEE GRANTS WILL NOT BE INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT PORTFOLIO GOING FORWARD.
  - Wildacres Retreat, 20050245, 2005 November 1-2006 November 1 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 4072
    Grant 20050245, Wildacres Retreat, $100,000. For a permanent endowment to support the William C. Friday Fellowship for human relations leadership program. 6/01/12: CHANGED TYPE OF SUPPORT CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING. GRANT NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT GRANT REPORTING GOING FORWARD.
  - Wildacres Retreat, 20050172, 2005 October 1-2006 October 1 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 4073
    Grant 20050172, Wildacres Retreat, $20,000. Trustee-recommended grant (Neill): For the Wildacres Leadership Inititative Endowment Fund. 9/1/11: CHANGED CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING SUPPORT. TRUSTEE GRANTS WILL NOT BE INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT PORTFOLIO GOING FORWARD.
  - Blue Grass Community Foundation, 20020002, 2002 March 12-2007 March 12 (Box 60, Folder 5, Box 61, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4210
    Grant 20020002, Blue Grass Community Foundation. $2.5 million to establish a donor-advised fund. (2 folders, folder 2 is in box 61)
  - California Community Foundation, 20030142, 2003 September 9-2007 September 9 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 4211
    Grant 20030142, California Community Foundation. $1,825,000 for donor-advised funds.
  - The Center for Public Integrity, 20040106, 2004 June 15-2007 June 15 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4212
    Grant 20040106, The Center for Public Integrity. $2 million partial challenge grant for operating support and a matching endowment grant to continue the center's investigative journalism.
  - Centre County Community Foundation, 20060037, 2006 March 14-2007 March 14 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 4213
    Grant 20060037, Centre County Community Foundation. $750,000 to increase the donor advised fund.
  - Community Foundation for Palm Beach and Martin Counties, 20030139, 2003 September 3-2007 September 9 (Box 62, Folder 3, Box 63, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4214
    Community Foundation for Palm Beach and Martin Counties, 20030139. $1.88 million for donor-advised funds. (2 folders, folder 2 is in box 63)
  - Community Foundation of Central Georgia, 20030140, 2003 September 9-2007 September 9 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 4215
    Community Foundation of Central Georgia, 20030140. $2 million for donor-advised funds (Macon GA Fund).
  - The Community Foundation of North Florida, 20040306, 2004 December 7-2007 December 7 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4216
    The Community Foundation of North Florida, 20040306. $2,575,000 to establish a donor-advised fund.
  - The Pennsylvania State University, 20050189, 2005 September 20-2007 September 20 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 4217
    The Pennsylvania State University, 20050189. $1.5 million to endow a Knight Chair in Sports Journalism and Society.
  - The Pewabic Society, 20040114, 2004 June 15-2007 June 15 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4218
    The Pewabic Society, 20040114. $450,000 to expand its ceramic art programming for Detroit youth. 8/11/11: WAS CODED AS ENDOWMENT. REMOVED CODING AS TYPE OF SUPPORT AND NOT INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT MANAGEMENT GOING FORWARD.
  - Virginia Coalition for Open Government, 20050045, 2005 May 1-2007 May 1 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 4219
    Virginia Coalition for Open Government, 20050045. $200,000 for a challenge grant to raise a permanent endowment.
  - Akron Art Museum, 20060027, 2006 March 14-2008 May 31 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 4452
    Grant 20060027, Akron Art Museum, $2,000,000. For the Create A Masterpiece campaign to expand the Akron Art Museum, enlarge its endowment, and name the new building in honor of John S. and James L. Knight.
  - Community Foundation for Palm Beach and Martin Counties, 20050093, 2005 July 1-2008 July 1 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 4453
    Grant 20050093, Community Foundation for Palm Beach and Martin Counties, $2,500,000. To increase the donor-advised fund accordingly as Palm Beach's designation has changed from a medium to large Knight community.
  - University of Michigan - Ann Arbor, 20020328, 2002 September 10-2008 September 10 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4457
    Grant 20020328, University of Michigan -Ann Arbor, $5,000,000. To name the Michigan program the Knight-Wallace Journalism Fellowships, and expand its endowment with a challenge grant.
  - Dade Community Foundation (now The Miami Foundation, Inc.), 20070031, 2007 March 12-2008 April 30 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 4454
    Grant 20070031, Dade Community Foundation (now The Miami Foundation, Inc.), $1,000,000. To strengthen the leadership ranks of the Miami region by responding to a challenge that will build an endowment for the acclaimed Miami Fellows Initiative.
  - Emma Willard School, 20070147, 2007 October 1-2008 October 1 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 4455
    Grant 20070147, Emma Willard School, $5,000. Trustee-Advised Grant (Crane): For endowment for scholarships. 9/1/11: CHANGED CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING SUPPORT. TRUSTEE GRANTS WILL NOT BE INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT PORTFOLIO GOING FORWARD.
  - School of Journalism and Mass Communication Foundation of North Carolina, 20070080, 2007 May 16-2008 July 31 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 5104
    Grant 20070080, School of Journalism and Mass Communication Foundation of North Carolina, $200,000 to expand the Knight Chair activities to digital media, and to hold an annual high-profile conference to amplify the chair's work.
  - Meadowbrook School of Weston, Inc., 20070183, 2007 November 1-2008 November 1 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 4456
    Grant 20070183, Meadowbrook School of Weston, Inc. $10,000. Trustee-Advised Grant (Austen): For endowment to support faculty - improve salaries, retirement benefits and professional development. 9/1/11: CHANGED CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING SUPPORT. TRUSTEE GRANTS WILL NOT BE INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT PORTFOLIO GOING FORWARD.
  - University of Washington, 20070102, 2007 August 1-2008 August 1 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4458
    Grant 20070102, University of Washington, $10,000. Trustee-Advised Grant (Crutchfield): To lead the creation of the Albert Black Endowed Award Fund, to help support efforts to have students work in the community. 9/1/11: CHANGED CODING FROM ENDOWMENT TO GENERAL OPERATING SUPPORT. TRUSTEE GRANTS WILL NOT BE INCLUDED IN ENDOWMENT PORTFOLIO GOING FORWARD.
  - Investigative Reporters and Editors, 20010247, 2001 September 11-2009 October 31 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 4685
    Grant 20010247, Investigative Reporters and Editors, $2,000,000. For a partial challenge for an IRE endowment and operating support.
  - Kent State University, 20060072, 2006 July 1-2009 March 31 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 4703
    Kent State University, 20060072, $150,000. To establish a Knight Chair in Scholastic Journalism to lead national efforts to revitalize high school journalism.
  - Meadowbrook School of Weston Inc., 20080104, 2008 August 11-2009 October 31 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 4686
    Grant 20080104, Meadowbrook School of Weston Inc., $10,000. Trustee-Advised Grant (Austen): For endowment to support facility; improve salaries, retirement benefits and professional development.
  - The Oak Clinic, 20080139, 2008 October 4-2009 September 30 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 4687
    Grant 20080139, The Oak Clinic. For the MS Endowment fund, $5,000. Trustee-Advised grant (Briggs).
  - The School of Journalism and Mass Communication Foundation of North Carolina, 20080095, 2008 July 1-2009 June 30 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    Knight File Number - 4688
    Grant 20080095, The School of Journalism and Mass Communication Foundation of North Carolina, $5,000. Trustee-Advised Grant (Neill): To endow the Hugh Morton Journalism Professorship.
  - Stephens College Endowment Foundation, 20080093, 2008 July 1-2009 June 30 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    Knight File Number - 4689
    Grant 20080093, Stephens College Endowment Foundation, $30,000. Trustee-Advised Grant (Powell): For an endowed professorship.
  - The School of Journalism and Mass Communication Foundation of North Carolina, 20100003, 2009-2010 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    Knight File Number - 5855
    Grant 20100003, The School of Journalism and Mass Communication Foundation of North Carolina, $250,000. To convert the existing James L. Knight Professorships to the James L. Knight Chair in Digital Advertising.
  - Yale University, 20070042, 2007 March 12-2010 August 31 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 4858
    Grant 20070042, Yale University, $2,500,000, to train the next generation's leading legal journalists and media lawyers by creating the Knight Law and Media Scholars.
  - Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press, 20050192, 2005 September 20-2010 September 20 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 4857
    Grant 20050192, Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press, $2,500,000, for an endowment campaign and operating support.
  - Arts and Science Council - Charlotte/Mecklenburg, 20060114, 2006 September 1-2011 September 1 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 4997
    Grant 20060114, Arts and Science Council - Charlote/Mecklenburg, $5,000,000 for an operating endowment to support extensive new cultural facilities in downtown Charlotte, including a 1,200 seat theater to be named for John S. and James L. Knight.
  - American Society of Newspaper Editors Foundation, 20060185, 2006 December 4-2012 December 31 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 5178
    Grant 20060185, American Society of Newspaper Editors Foundation, $3,400,000, to increase public awareness of the importance of open government and endow Sunshine Week by creating the Knight First Amendment Fund.
  - Miami Art Museum of Dade County Association (now Jorge M. Perez Art Museum of Miami Dade County), 20070264, 2007 December 10-2012 December 31 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 5182
    Grant 20070264, Miami Art Museum of Dade County Association (now Jorge M. Perez Art Museum of Miami Dade County Inc.), $10,000,000, to help create a vibrant museum culture in Miami by endowing Art for all Miami, an art education program that will lower the barrier to entry to the visual arts by takng 40,000 students to class at the museum each year.
  - Miami Foundation, Inc., 20110120, 2011 July 22-2012 June 30 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 5183
    Grant 20110120, Miami Foundation, Inc. $2,100,000, to create a journalism education innovation fund that will initially take on a long-term national News21 project at Arizona State University.
  - Michigan State University, 20050034, 2005 March 15-2012 April 30 (Box 70, Folder 1, Box 71)
    Knight File Number - 5184
    Grant 20050034, Michigan State University, $2,200,000 to expand the Knight Center for Environmental Journalism in partnership with the university and launch an endowment campaign. 2 folders. Folder 2 is in box 71.
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, 20070265, 2007 December 10-2012 December 31 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 5185
    Grant 20070265, Museum of Contemporary Art, $5,000,000, to solidify Miami as a cultural destination through development of cutting-edge contemporary arts exhibitions supported in whole or part by an endowment that provides a sustainable base of funding.
  - New World Symphony, 20070266, 2007 December 10-2012 December 31 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 5186
    Grant 20070266, New World Symphony, $5,000,000, to enable a unique orchestral academy to solidify its role as cultural icon by creation of a Knight New Media Endowment that will help the organization capitalize on technology and explore new performance formats.
  - Miami Foundation, 20090248, 2009 December 9-2014 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 5511
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Open in 2025
    Grant 20090248, the Miami Foundation, $5,500,000, to supplement an existing donor-advised fund.
  - Akron Community Foundation, 20090247, 2009 December 7-2014 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 5510
    Grant 20090247, Akron Community Foundation, $5,500,000, to supplement an existing donor-advised fund.
  - The Community Foundation of North Florida, 20090274, 2010 January 1-2015 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 5858
    Restricted - Open in 2026
    Grant 20090274, The Community Foundation of North Florida, $2,500,000. To supplement an existing donor-advised fund for the purpose of supporting informed and engaged communities
  - Long Beach Community Foundation, 20090265, 2010 January 1-2015 December 31 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 5857
    Long Beach Community Foundation, 20090265, $2,500,000 to supplement an existing donor-advised fund.
  - Queens University of Charlotte, 20100196, 2010 October 1-2015 December 31 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 5882
    Queens University of Charlotte, 20100196, $5.75 million. To name the James L. Knight School of Communication at Queens University of Charlotte and establish its special endowed mission of teaching digital and media literacy to students and the community.
- Manuals, 1989-1990; 4; 0.19 Cubic Feet 1 half-letter box
  There are two manuals in this subgroup. The Program Policy Manual (1989) outlines the history of Knight Foundation and its programs, and discusses guidelines for the program staff in dealing with grant requests for each program. It includes documents such as the Foundation's Articles of Incorporation, Code of Regulations, Conflict of Interest Policy, Statement of Purpose, and Guidelines from the latest Annual Report, as well as key passages illustrating program policies from Board minutes, committee meeting minutes and memos.
  The Program Assistants Manual (1990) outlines the responsibilities of a program assistant, and gives examples of grant write-up, grids, memos to the Distribution Committee, and summaries of proposals. It also contains a list of eligible Knight cities.
  - Program Policy Manual, 1989 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Knight File Number - 281
    Contains history of Knight Foundation (Articles of Incorporation, Code of Regulations, Conflict of Interest Policy, Statement of Purpose, and Guidelines from latest Annual Report). Additional materials excerpted from board minutes, committee meeting minutes, and memos are included on the following subjects: annual support, Arts & Culture, Community Foundations, Deficits and Environmental Emergencies, Education, Endowments, Films, Guidelines, Cities Program Carryover, Health Programs/Hospitals, Individuals and Disqualified Persons, Journalism, Memorials, Minimum Grants, Multi-year grants, Public Broadcasting, Religious Organizations, Tax-Supported Institutions, Trustee Discretionary Grants, United Way.
  - Program Assistants Manual, 1990 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Knight File Number - 282
    Handbook for program assistants, including responsibilities, and examples of the following: writeup format, green data sheet, index for distribution committee packet, memos to distribution committee, summary of proposals, annual support report, treasurer's grids, staff rejections report, president's cover memo for board packet, distribution committee memo for board packet, Knight Foundation description, associates' grids, philanthropic journals report, Tony Ridder reports, Akron foundations report, proposal stamp, eligible cities, Grants Manager screen printouts, associates' review form, 990 IRS report, Akron foundations group report (rejected and pending proposals), associate grids (following proposal deadline).
- Meetings, 1990-2007; 5; 0.38 Cubic Feet 2 half-letter document boxes
  - Program Staff Meeting Minutes, 1996 September 19-2001 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Knight File Number - 1069
    The minutes of Program Staff Meetings include discussions about computer systems, procedures and processes in grantmaking, working with community advisors, Gifts for Windows, and other staff issues and concerns.
  - Program Staff Retreat Materials, 1997 July 29-1997 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Knight File Number - 4004
    Memos and agenda for the first program staff retreat. Includes survey of participants and Team reports.
  - Meeting of Program Leadership, 2007 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Knight File Number - 4064
    Agenda for the program leadership meeting, which was designed to increase clarity about the characteristics and attributes of transformational grants.
  - Remarks to Foundation for the Carolinas, 1990 April 18 (Box 1)
    Knight File Number - 129
    Remarks made in Charlotte, NC.
- Program-Related Files, 1975-2019; 6; 32.9 Cubic Feet 94 containers
  - Arts, 2010-2017; 1; 0.19 Cubic Feet 1 half-letter box
    - Knight Arts Inside/Out Initiative, 2010-2014 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Knight File Number - 5354
      Restricted - Open 2025
      Background on the Inside/Out Initiative, which places framed reproductions of art on streets and in parks. The initiative began in Detroit, and will move to Akron, Miami, and Philadelphia and possibly other KF communities.
    - Grant Acknowledgment Letters, 2012 July 30-2013 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Knight File Number - 5458
      Sample of letters to Dennis Scholl and the Arts team in appreciation of KF support of the arts.
    - Email News Alerts, 2015 February 11-2016 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Knight File Number - 5484
      Restricted - Open 2027
      Email news alert re: Dennis Scholl's Instagram account; program alert: conversation with artists Steven and William Ladd at Miami Dade College Museum of Art sponsored by KF.
    - Knight Arts Challenge Miami, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Knight File Number - 5995
      Restricted - Open 2028
      Booklet listing Knight Arts Challenge Miami winners for 2017. 43 winning ideas